http://www.smoothjazz.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
SmoothJazz.com Privacy Policy
Personally identifying information that you provide to SmoothJazz.com will not be made available to third parties outside of SmoothJazz.com and affiliated websites such as SmoothLounge.com, SmoothTravel.net and JazzWeekender.com, without your explicit permission.
SmoothJazz.com collects personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. Your personally identifying information will be used to personalize your experience with SmoothJazz.com Web sites, or for such other purposes as are described at any point where SmoothJazz.com collects this information from you.
SmoothJazz.com may make aggregate information about our customers (e.g. overall statistics) available to third parties for advertising and other purposes. Information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential.
Personally identifying information which you choose to provide to another party or Web site will be subject to their privacy policy. For example, if you purchase goods or services online from a merchant you found while searching SmoothJazz.com, information you provide to that merchant is subject to their privacy policy rather than ours.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site, like what items you have in a "shopping cart" for an online store. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide great features for their customers.
SmoothJazz.com has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the SmoothJazz.com service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to SmoothJazz.com always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of SmoothJazz.com service may not function properly if you refuse cookies.
Links to Sites
Users should be aware that when you are on SmoothJazz.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from SmoothJazz.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or a SmoothJazz.com search result, the "click" takes you off SmoothJazz.com site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use SmoothJazz.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up!
SmoothJazz.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the SmoothJazz.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.
Making Contact
When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to the concerns you write to us with. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within SmoothJazz.com to help us respond to your concerns and improve  SmoothJazz.com.
